Remember that in the last video,
在上个视频中
we set up a Lambda function,
我们设置了一个 Lambda 函数
making sure to give it permission to access
并使其能够访问 SageMaker 端点
a SageMaker endpoint and then we tested it to make sure it was working.
然后测试该函数 确保它能够正常运行
In this video, we're going to create an endpoint that triggers our Lambda function.
在本视频中 我们将创建一个能触发该 Lambda 函数的端点
That is, we're going to create an endpoint or an interface that
即创建一个网络应用能够使用的端点或接口
our web app can use in order to send data to our Lambda function.
从而向 Lambda 函数发送数据
To do that, we're going to use API Gateway.
我们将使用 API Gateway
If we go back to the Amazon console and then scroll down all the way
切换到 Amazon 控制台 然后一直向下滚动到
to Networking &amp; Content Delivery, select API Gateway.
Networking &amp; Content Delivery 选择“API Gateway”
If your gateway lets you create
通过 API Gateway 可以创建一个端点
an endpoint which you can use to trigger all sorts of things.
并使用该端点触发各种对象
For this example, we're going to use it to trigger a Lambda function.
在此示例中 我们将用端点触发 Lambda 函数
So, click on Get Started and then click on Okay.
点击“Get Started” 然后点击“Okay”
We would like to create a new API and our API's name is going to be sentimentAnalysis.
我们将创建一个新的 API 名称为 sentimentAnalysis
Then we click on Create API.
然后点击“Create API”
So, we have a new API.
我们有了新的 API
Currently it doesn't do anything.
目前它不能执行任何操作
Let's add an action,
我们添加一个操作
which we can do by clicking on
点击“Actions”下拉菜单
the Actions drop-down menu and then selecting Create Method.
然后选择“Create Method”
Which method? We are going to use a post method.
使用哪个方法呢？我们将使用 POST 方法
Now this involves knowing a little bit about the HTTP protocol;
这里需要对 HTTP 协议有所了解
however, that is a bit beyond the scope of this course.
这已经超出了这门课程的范畴
So, we want to create a post action.
我们将创建一个 POST 操作
Once we've selected post,
选择“POST”后
we click on the check mark and a new post action has been created for our endpoint.
选中该复选框 系统为端点新建了一个 POST 操作
What kind of integration type would we like?
我们想要什么样的交互？
Well, we would like it to integrate with a Lambda function.
我们希望它能与 Lambda 函数交互
Furthermore, we would like to use Lambda Proxy integration.
此外 我们将选择“Use Lambda Proxy integration”
This means that our API is not going to do any sort of data checking whatsoever.
这表示我们的 API 不会检查数据
It is just going to send whatever it receives to
只是将接收的任何数据发送给 Lambda 函数
the Lambda function and then return back to
然后将 Lambda 函数输出的内容
the caller anything that the Lambda function spits out.
返回给调用者
Which Lambda function are we going to use?
使用哪个 Lambda 函数？
The one that we created earlier called sentiment Lambda function.
使用之前创建的 sentiment_lambda_function 函数
Once we have made sure that we are integrating with Lambda function,
指定要与 Lambda 函数交互
made sure that we are using Lambda Proxy integration,
使用 Lambda Proxy integration
and selected the Lambda function we want to use, click on "Save".
并选择我们要使用的 Lambda 函数后 点击“Save”
Yes, we would like to add permission for our API to access our sentiment Lambda function.
是的 我们想让 API 有权访问 sentiment_lambda_function
So, we've created an API and we've given that API something to do.
我们创建了一个 API 并为其设定了操作
Now we need to actually deploy it.
现在需要部署该 API
Again, if we click on the "Actions" drop-down and select "Deploy API."
点击“Actions”下拉菜单 然后选择“Deploy API”
We need to give it a deployment stage.
我们需要设定部署阶段
Now this has something to do with the different types
部署阶段是指
of environments you might need to deploy this API in.
部署 API 的不同环境
For example, if you just wanted to test something internally,
例如 如果要在内部进行测试
you might deploy this to a test stage.
可以部署到测试阶段
For us, we're just going to call our deployment stage prod, for production.
对我们来说 我们将部署到生产阶段
To do that, we select the drop-down menu and add a new stage.
点击该下拉菜单 然后添加新的阶段
The name of that stage is going to be prod.
命名为“prod”
Once we've done that, we can click on "Deploy" and that's it.
然后点击“Deploy” 搞定
Our API is now deployed.
API 已经部署了
This is the URL that our API can be accessed at.
这是访问该 API 的 URL
So, if we send a post request to this URL,
如果向此 URL 发送 POST 请求
the body of that post request will get sent our Lambda function and
该请求的 body 将发送给 Lambda 函数
our Lambda function will return to us whatever the results of our model is.
Lambda 函数将返回模型的结果
So, now we have a Lambda function that does the data processing we need,
现在我们有了处理数据的 Lambda 函数
we have a model that creates the prediction we need,
以及进行预测的模型
and we've created an API that allows us to access all of those things.
并且创建了能够访问它们的 API
Next, we're going to launch the web app using our newly created API.
接下来 我们将使用新创建的 API 启动网络应用